Guide to the Creative Time Records MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 1974-2012; 204.08 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 75 manuscript boxes, 275 jewel cases, 22 box binders, 8 oversized flat boxes, 9 oversized folders, 5 shared record cartons, 2 tall manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 shared flat box, and 1 shared casset
  - Art on the Plaza 3: Peace by Zhang Huang, September 2003-April 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40870
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 68, Folder 6, Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Prints (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 145, Dvd 179.0128)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0127)
  - "Blur '04" Working Group -- Correspondence, October 2003 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Halloween Hell House by Multiple Artists -- Co-Sponsored by Deitch Projects -- Flyer, October 2003 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - The 59th Minute: PDPal (Personal Digital Pal) by Marina Zurkow, Scott Paterson, and Julian Bleecker -- Co-Presented by Panasonic, October-December 2003
    - Electronic Records, cuid40911
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 69, Folder 4-5)
  - Official Welcome by Andrea Fraser -- Co-Presented with Printed Matter, December 2003
    - Electronic Records, December 2003; cuid40912
    - Correspondence and Photographs (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Grand Central's 90th Anniversary Celebration Proposal -- Unrealized Project, circa 2003 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - The 59th Minute by Hiraki Sawa, Janaina Tschape, and The Neistat Brothers, January-April 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40913
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 23)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dream Sequence, Dwelling, and Mousetrap (Box 147, Dvd 179.0308)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dream Sequence and Dwelling (Box 148, Dvd 179.0378)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dream Sequence and Dwelling (Box 148, Dvd 179.0415)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dream Sequence, Dwelling, and Mousetrap (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0307)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dream Sequence and Dwelling (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0377)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dream Sequence and Dwelling (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0414)
  - "New Sound, New York" Presented by TimeOut New York and The Kitchen -- Co-Sponsored by Creative Time -- Press, March-May 2004 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Art on the Plaza 4: Breath by Shirazeh Houshiary with Pip Horne, May 2004-January 2005
    - Programs, Press, Correspondence, and Photographs (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Blueprints (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 18)
  - Blue Moon by O+A (Sam Audinger and Bruce Odland) -- Co-Presented by the World Financial Center and the Battery Park City Authority, May-August 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40914
    - Programs, Press, Correspondence, and Photographs (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 17)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Press with Stephanie Simon (Box 149, Dvd 179.0471)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Press with Stephanie Simon (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0470)
  - The Dreamland Artist Club by Multiple Artists -- Coney Island, June-September 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40915
    - Programs, Press, Photographs, and Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 3-5)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 24-27)
  - The 59th Minute: Who's Afraid of Blue, Red, and Green? by Gunther Selichar, et al., June-September 2004
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0248)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0247)
  - Plan B by Rudolf Stingel -- Co-Presented by Art Production Fund and Metropolitan Transit Authority Arts for Transit -- Program, July 2004 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Imagine Arts Festival Participant -- Program, August 2004 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Operation Urban Terrain (OUT) by Anne-Marie Schleiner -- Program and Press, August 2004 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - When Worlds Collide Presented by The Moth -- In Conjunction with Creative Time and Times Square Alliance -- Program, August 2004 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Freedom of Expression National Monument by Laurie Hawkinson, John Malpede, and Erika Rothenberg -- Co-Presented by the Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, August-November 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40916
    - Programs, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 19-20)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBS Sunday Morning Coverage (Box 147, Dvd 179.0294)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0489)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CBS Sunday Morning Coverage (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0293)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0488)
  - Imitation of Christ Retail Store -- Program and Press, September 2004 (Box 71, Folder 7, Box 5, Folder 252)
  - For New York City: Planes and Projections by Jenny Holzer, October-November 2004
    - Programs, Press, Photographs, and Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 21-22)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 1 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0585)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0593)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Part 1 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0584)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Part 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0592)
  - The 59th Minute: The Forest by Carlos Amorales -- Co-Presented by Panasonic and in Conjunction with Mexico Now Festival, November 2004-January 2005
    - Electronic Records, cuid40917
    - Programs, Press, Correspondence, and Photographs (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 28)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 147, Dvd 179.0310)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Televisa New York (Box 149, Dvd 179.0483)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Televisa New York (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0482)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0309)
    - Video Recording -- Original, 2003 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0669)
  - Art in Times Square by Nina Katchadourian, Ellen Harvey, and K48 -- Unrealized Project, 2004
    - Electronic Records, cuid40918
    - Proposal and Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - Revised K48 Media Outpost -- Parks Department Submission (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Blueprints for K48 Installation (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - NUEVOS RICOS=USA, January 2005
    - Electronic Records, cuid40919
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Consumer's Guide to Times Square Advertising by Christine Hill -- Co-Presented with Times Square Alliance, January-April 2005
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 253, Box 72, Folder 5-6)
    - Hand-Drawn Map of Times Square (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - The 59th Minute: Conditions of Anonymity by Kimsooja -- Co-Presented with Panasonic, March-June 2005
    - Programs, Press, Photographs, and Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 33)
  - Art on the Plaza 5: Look and See by Jim Hodges, May-October 2005
    - Programs, Photographs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 36)
    - Blueprints (Flat-file-folder 10)
  - The Dreamland Artist Club by Multiple Artists -- Coney Island, June-October 2005
    - Programs, Press, Photographs, and Correspondence (Box 73, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 29-31)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Stephanie Simon (Box 145, Dvd 179.0130)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 145, Dvd 179.0132)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Stephanie Simon (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0129)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0131)
  - The Art Parade 2005 -- Co-Presented with Deitch Projects and Paper Magazine -- Press, September 2005 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - For the City by Jenny Holzer, September-October 2005
    - Programs, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 35)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Raw Footage, 2004 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0587)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Jenny Holzer -- Bobst Library, NYU, November 2005 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0589)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Jenny Holzer -- Political Art -- Reuters (Box 151, Dvd 179.0595)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Raw Footage, 2004 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0586)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Jenny Holzer -- Bobst Library, NYU (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0588)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Jenny Holzer -- Political Art -- Reuters (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0594)
  - The 59th Minute: Three Projects by Song Dong, September-November 2005
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Song Dong -- Evaporating Art -- Reuters (Box 148, Dvd 179.0372)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Song Dong -- Evaporating Art -- Reuters (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0371)
  - The Plain of Heaven by Multiple Artists, October-November 2005
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
    - Map of the Highline and Blueprints by Zaha Hadid (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 34)
  - The 59th Minute: Countdowns by Aïda Ruilova -- Press and Programs, December 2005-March 2006 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Unrealized Projects -- Correspondence and Proposals, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Billboards by Marilyn Minter -- Postcards, March 2006 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - The 59th Minute by Multiple Artists -- Programs, Press, and Correspondence, March-June 2006 (Box 74, Folder 6, Box 5, Folder 254)
  - Broken Screen Happening by Doug Aitken, et al. -- Co-Sponsored by Hermés -- Correspondence, Programs, and Press, May 2006 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - The Dreamland Artist Club at the Mermaid Parade -- Press and Correspondence, June 2006 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Strange Powers by Multiple Artists, July-September 2006
    - Electronic Records, cuid40920
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - The Art Parade 2006 by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Deitch Projects and Paper Magazine -- Press, September 2006 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Who Cares by Multiple Artists -- Correspondence and Press, September-December 2006 (Box 75, Folder 2-4, Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Live from the New York Public Library with Paul Chan and Kathy Kelly -- Program, November 2006 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Sky Is the Limit by Haluk Akakçe -- Co-Presented by the Las Vegas Arts Commission -- Correspondence, Press, and Programs, November 2006 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - The Urban Visual Recording Machine by Hjalti Karlsson and Jan Wilker -- Press and Programs, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - The Battery Republic -- Project Assisted by Creative Time -- Press and Program, circa 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Unrealized Projects -- "Telephone Art" and Carsten Höller Project -- Proposals and Correspondence, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Art on the Plaza 6: Air gets into everything even nothing and Get up girl a sun is running the world by Ugo Rondione -- Press and Program, December 2006-January 2007 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - sleepwalkers by Doug Aitken, January-February 2007
    - Electronic Records, cuid40921
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 76, Folder 8-9, Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - The Rape of the Sabine Women by Eve Sussman and the Rufus Corporation, February 2007
    - Electronic Records, cuid40922
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 33 Watercolors for 33 Years by Mark Malmgren -- Programs and Correspondence, May 2007 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - One Day It Will Please Us to Remember Even This by Multiple Artists, May 2007
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Placards (Box 100, Box 101)
  - Creative Time: The Book--33 Years of Public Art in New York, 2007
    - Electronic Records, cuid40897
    - Drafts, Galleys, and Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 255, Box 78, Folder 1-4)
    - Unused Prints (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Photographs (Roll-storage 132)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Calvin Trillin (Box 145, Cd 179.0114)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Calvin Trillin (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0113)
  - Six Actions for New York City by Multiple Artists -- Programs, Press, and Correspondence, May-November 2007 (Box 79, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - The Art Parade 2007 by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Deitch Projects and Paper Magazine -- Poster, September 2007 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - A Psychic Vacuum by Mike Nelson -- Programs and Press, September-October 2007 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Waiting for Godot in New Orleans by Paul Chan -- Program and Press, November 2007 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - City Hall Project -- Unrealized -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2007 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Hey Hey Glossolalia by Multiple Artists -- Program and Press, May 2008 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Playing the Building by David Byrne, May-August 2008
    - Electronic Records, cuid40923
    - Banner (Box 103)
    - Photographs, Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - At 44 1/2 by Multiple Artists, June-September 2008
    - Electronic Records, cuid40924
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Democracy in America: The National Campaign by Multiple Artists, June-September 2008
    - Electronic Records, cuid40925
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 79, Folder 8, Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Guerrilla Girls Poster (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Fair and Balanced News -- "Freedom" (Box 150, Dvd 179.0525)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Fair and Balanced News -- "Freedom" (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0524)
  - At 44 1/2 by Multiple Artists -- Programs, October 2009 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Key to the City by Paul Ramirez Jonas -- Programs, 2010 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Living as Form, September-October 2011
    - Alternate ROOTS (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Basurama (Box 80, Folder 7-8)
    - Appalshop -- Electronic Records, cuid40926
    - Appalshop -- Programs and Press (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
    - Céline Condorelli and Gavin Wade (Box 80, Folder 9-10)
    - Cornerstone Theater Company (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - El Cerro Project, September-October 2011 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Free Southern Theater, September-October 2011 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Ithaca Hours Local Currency Project, September-October 2011 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Surasi Kusolwong (Box 81, Folder 4-6, Box 82, Folder 1, Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Bronwyn Lace and Anthea Mays (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Long March Project -- Electronic Records, cuid40927
    - Long March Project -- Program (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles Poverty Department (Box 82, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 10)
    - MadeIn Company (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Mammalian Diving Reflex -- "Haircuts for Children" (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Angela Melitopoulos (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Money Nations (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - NSK (Neue Slowenische Kunst) (Box 82, Folder 8, Box 83, Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Nuts Society (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Oda Projesi (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Park Fiction (Box 83, Folder 4-6)
    - Bik Van der Pol (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Sarai and Ankur (Box 84, Folder 2-3)
    - Slanguage (Box 84, Folder 4, Box 102)
    - Apolonija Sustersic (Box 84, Folder 5, Box 102)
    - Mierle Laderman Ukeles (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Urban Bush Women -- Electronic Records, cuid40928
    - Urban Bush Women -- Programs and Press (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Women on Waves (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Multiple Artists (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Space Program: Mars by Tom Sachs -- Co-Presented by Park Avenue Armory -- Program, May-June 2012 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Art in the Anchorage, Undated
    - Negatives (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Poster (Box Shared Fales 081, Folder 3)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Closing Party -- Tape #1 (Box 145, Cd 179.0077)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Closing Party -- Tape #2 (Box 144, Cd 179.0050)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Closing Party -- Tape #1 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0076)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Closing Party -- Tape #2 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0049)
  - Art on the Beach, undated
    - Electronic Records, cuid40869
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Master (Box 151, Dvd 179.0702)
    - Film -- Original (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0698)
  - Undated and Unidentified Materials
    - Postcards, Correspondence, and Flyers (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Negatives (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "#4, 6/28" (Box 145, Dvd 179.0146)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0164)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0555)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "1st Tape R" (Box 146, Dvd 179.0200)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "#4, 6/28" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0145)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0163)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "1st Tape R" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0199)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0554)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0650)
- Series II: Grants and Development, 1974-2007; 37.74 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 10 manuscript boxes, 6 box binders, 20 jewel cases, 6 oversized folders, and 1 flat box; 95 kilobytes in 7 computer files; 6 CDs; 10 DVD-R; 3 DVDs; 3 VHS; 4 U-matic; 3 Hi8
  Arranged first alphabetically by funding organization, then chronologically by fundraising event.
  This series contains grant applications and reports for grants received; fundraising and development materials (benefit invitations, programs, photographs, and slides; appeals to organizations for sponsorships; and individual appeals); and general fundraising inquiries. These materials describe how Creative Time has been able to support its commissioned projects.
  - Altria Group, 1997-2007 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - The Andy Warhol Foundation for the VIsual Arts, 1989-1999 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Arts International, November 2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - AT&T Foundation, 1988-1994 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Buhl Foundation, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Capezio/Ballet Makers Dance Foundation, 1985-2002 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1996-2001 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Con Edison, 1981-1995 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Chemical Bank, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Citibank, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, Suitcase Fund, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - Daniel Langlois Foundation, 1999-2003 (Box 86, Folder 8, Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Department of Citywide Administrative Services, 1977-1991 (Box 12, Folder 152-166)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, Council of the City of New York, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Étant donnés (The French-American Fund for Contemporary Art), 1996-2006 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Good Works Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - The Gunk Foundation, 1996-2006 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - The Harkness Foundation for Dance, 1992-2004 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Heathcote Art Foundation, 1992-2001 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Howard Gilman Foundation, 1992-2002 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Independence Community Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1994-2004 (Box 87, Folder 10, Box 88, Folder 1)
  - J.P. Morgan, 1997-2001 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Jules and Doris Stein Foundation/Art Matters, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1986-2000 (Box 13, Folder 176, Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Lef Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Mary Cary Trust, 1984-1995 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Meet the Composer and Institute of Museum Studies, 1977-1986 (Box 12, Folder 167-170)
  - The Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1974-1997
    - Electronic Records, cuid40898
    - Applications, Reports, and Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 1-40, Box 7, Folder 41-74, Box 8, Folder 75-98, Box 9, Folder 99-119)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Music Samples -- Part 1, Spring 1991 (Box 144, Cd 179.0068)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Music Samples -- Part 2, Spring 1991 (Box 144, Cd 179.0069)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Selections for NEA Review, 1991 (Box 144, Cd 179.0052)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Live Recordings for NEA Music Program FY90, 1987-1988 (Box 145, Cd 179.0088)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Live Recordings for NEA Music Program FY92, 1988-1991 (Box 145, Cd 179.0116)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- NEA Music Tape Copy (Box 144, Cd 179.0046)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Music Samples, Spring (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0067)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Selections for NEA Review, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0051)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Live Recordings for NEA Music Program FY90, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0087)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Live Recordings for NEA Music Program FY92, 1988-1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0115)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- NEA Music Tape Copy (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0045)
  - New York Community Trust, 1984-1991 (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1974-1990 (Box 10, Folder 120-144, Box 11, Folder 145-151)
  - Panasonic, 2001-2006 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Pew Charitable Trust, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Reader's Digest Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Roy and Niuta Titus Foundation, 1997-2006 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Letters of Inquiry to Grant-Funding Institutions, 1977-2006 (Box 13, Folder 184-189, Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Forms, Requests, and Budgets, 1975-1984 (Box 13, Folder 190-197)
  - Annual Appeals and Individual Giving, 1985-2000 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Ruckus Manhattan Benefit, December 1981 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Holiday Gift Certificates, 1982-1983 (Box 142, Folder 15, Box 88, Folder 9)
  - "Co-Producer of the Avant-Garde" Appeal, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 54, Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Benefit Art Sales, 1984-1985
    - Programs, Invitations, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 56-57, Folder 66, Box 15, Folder 65, Box 88, Folder 11, Box 114, Folder Sleeves 18-21)
    - Slides (Box 114, Folder Sleeves 18-21)
    - Negatives, May 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Creative Times, Vol. 1, #2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Benefit Dance Party and Surprise Cocktail Party for Anita Contini, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 12-13)
  - Gala Benefit -- Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1987
    - Programs, Invitations, Press, and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 78, Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Gretchen Langheld (Box 148, Dvd 179.0403)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- John Torreano (Box 149, Dvd 179.0469)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Gretchen Langheld (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0402)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- John Torreano (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0468)
  - 15th Anniversary Halloween Party Benefit -- Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, October 1988
    - Correspondence, Programs, Invitations, and Press (Box 2, Folder 90, Folder 92, Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 139, Folder 12-14)
    - Slides (Box 118, Folder Sleeves 27-28)
  - Benefit Auction and Holiday Mailing, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 166, Box 18, Folder 202)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration -- Apollo Theater, July 1994
    - Electronic Records, cuid40867
    - Programs, Invitations, Correspondence, and Press (Box 5, Folder 231, Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 12-13)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Folder: Sleeves 20-25)
    - Posters (Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 9)